



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

**♠** Message

• • •

Huong Tran · 3rd

Founder and Director at Vietnam Campus Engage

Vietnam · 327 connections · Contact info

Vietnam Campus Engage



**Clark University** 

# About

Passion and expertise lies with social change through interpretation civic engagement into higher education; bridging universities to community to address social issues and to transform the youth into a generation of global citizenship. One of the leaders of the movement of engagement education in Vietnam recently.

... see more

# Activity

Posts Huong created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

#### See all activity

# Experience

#### **Founder and Director**

Vietnam Campus Engage · Full-time
Dec 2019 – Present
· 1 yr 5 mos
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Vietnam Campus Engage is a resource center for the Vietnamese universities which are committed to advance engagement learning and to build up a generation of global citizenship.

Its mission is to foster the environment for the development of community engaged learning and for addressing the needs of community by building capacity and partnerships between higher education institutions, faculties, students, community organizations and public entities while yearning for a better and sustainable society for all.

#### **Director of Non-Profit**

CAO Social Enterprise · Full-time Oct 2018 – Nov 2019 · 1 yr 2 mos

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Develop organizational identity, strategies and plans for the start-up social enterprise which focuses on sponsoring and capacity building other non-profit and social welfare organizations.

Manage projects/programs and consult to Board of Directors

#### Founding Director and Senior Advisor - Center for Service-Learning

University of Economics and Finance of Ho Chi Minh City · Full-time Jan 2018 – Aug 2019

· 1 yr 8 mos

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Establish the Center for Service-Learning and its procedures for service-learning/community engaged-learning in the university;

Develop, design and manage service-learning/community engaged-learning projects/assignment activities/courses in which include both learning objectives and outcomes and community serving objectives/outcomes;

Build and develop partnership between the university and community organizations, national and international universities committed in engagement education ... see more

#### **Director of Center for Service-Learning**

Hoa Sen University (Not for Profit) · Full-time
May 2016 – Aug 2017
· 1 yr 4 mos

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Plan, build procedures and lead the center of service-learning, the first center of this kind in Vietnam at that time;

Build partnership between university, faculty members and students with community organizations with activities/projects/assignments/internships... that address community needs;

Integrate service-learning into mainstream academic courses by procedures of curriculum building and academic capacity building in term of engagement education.

#### **Editor**

Thời báo Kinh tế Sài Gòn · Full-time May 2010 – Dec 2015 · 5 yrs 8 mos Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Managing the international economic pages

# Education

#### **Clark University**



Master of Arts - MA, International Development and Social Change 2005 – 2007

#### **Hue Teaching College, Department of Foreign Language**

Bachelor's degree, English 1990 – 1995

# Licenses & certifications

## **Ford Fellowship Award**



## Interests

#### **AmCham Vietnam**



#### SGT



**VNG Corporation** 



54,020 followers

## **British Chamber of Commerce Singapore (BritCham)**

7,191 followers



#### **EuroCham Vietnam**

24,355 followers



#### IARSLCE



# People also viewed



Barak Ekshtein •3rd 📊

Founder at TONTOTON

Connect



**Nguyễn Hoa ∙**3rd

Country Director at Population Services International

Connect



John N. •2nd

Senior Technical Consultant - Transfer High Tech European Plastic, Rubber, Silicone Machinery & Auxiliaries in Vietnam

Connect



**Loi Thi Nguyen •**3rd GESI Manager

Connect



Thu Yen Cao •3rd

Environmental Specialist at Vietnam Initiative for Energy Transition

Connect

**∨**Show more

# People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Student at Ton Duc Thang University

Connect

## **∨**Show more



Add new skills with these courses



corporate Event Video: Producing Company Meetings and Presentations

4,302 viewers



Virtual Apprentice: Being a Great Production Assistant (PA)

2,203 viewers



Filmmaking Tips Weekly

11,715 viewers

**Show more on LinkedIn Learning** 





LinkedIn Corporation © 2021







Search messages After April 15, 2021, your read receipts and typing indicators setting will expand to all messages, including InMails and Message Requests.

Manage settings Got it